We rise together as our destiny unfolds
随着命运的展开 就让我们一同迎战
We face the darkness and our trials are yet untold
而考验尚未结束 我们仍需直面黑暗
Through the shadows of despair
穿过绝望的阴影
Oh in silence hopes we share
在沉默中 我们共享希望
To chase our dreams that we've declared
只为追逐我们宣告中的理想
We glimpse through our eyes
我们曾尝试多看一眼
Yet fools blind our sights
却被无知蒙蔽了视线
Can't make what they say
既然听不懂他们的注解
We'll find our way we'll find our way
那就由我们找寻自己该走的路
Heads up The wheels are spinning
请注意 命运的车轮正在转动
Across the plains in valleys deep
跨越平原 穿过深谷
To dawn the wheels that sing
向着黎明 这车轮行滚滚而行歌唱着
An unending dream
一个无尽的梦
Heads up the tracks are running
请注意 轨道已然在运转
Across the plains where shadows hide
穿过阴霾藏匿的平原
We run we stride whoa oh
我们奔跑 我们向前
In the face of fear and plight and yet we hold our ground
面对恐惧和困境 我们依然坚守阵地
In life we stand and strive our victory is found
历久弥坚 胜利定会在望
And the storms we've weathered through
我们已穿越风雨
And we hope in the light of truth
只希望能沐浴在真理的光芒中
To break free from chains and come anew
挣脱枷锁 重获新生
Heads up The wheels are spinning
请注意 命运的车轮正在转动
Across the plains in valleys deep
跨越平原 穿过深谷
To dawn the wheels that sing
向着黎明 这车轮行滚滚而行歌唱着
An unending dream
一个无尽的梦
Heads up the tracks are running
请注意 轨道已然在运转
Across the plains where shadows hide
穿过阴霾藏匿的平原
We run we stride whoa oh
我们奔跑 我们向前
Heads up A steady rhythm
抬起头 跟着坚定的节奏
A destination that's ever near
终点已近在咫尺
It comes Stride to our kingdom
迈向我们的理想之地
And see the light of day
让一切重见曙光
Heads up the wheels are singing
请注意 命运的车轮正在歌唱
The whispers and secrets they'd keep
他们保守着苦痛的秘密和私语
To hope We bound whoa oh
而我们终将迎来希望
Break free we chased our dreams beneath the starry night
挣脱束缚 我们在星空下追逐梦想
In the face of god we rose as one
面对神灵 我们团结一致 奋勇向前